<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Exer2_Laxamana_B4L</string>
    <string name="title_text">Which Monogatari Character are you?</string>
    <string name="Start_image">start_image</string>
    <string name="bio_text">..</string>
    <string name="start_btn">Start</string>
    <string name="retry_btn">Retry</string>
    <string name="hachikuji_data"> Mayoi Hachikuji is the ghost of a fifth-grade elementary school girl who was killed in a traffic accident while trying to reach her mothers home. Since her death, she became an oddity who has haunted people that have the urge to avoid going home. Mayoi came from a broken family, with her mother divorcing from her father at an early age. After the divorce, her father was granted custody over Mayoi, and the lack of contact with her mother eventually made the young Mayoi forget what her mother looked like. Longing to see her mother, Mayoi decided to travel to look for her mothers house on her own. Sadly, during her search for the address of her mothers home she was involved in a truck accident, killing her at the day before Mothers Day, on May 14. After becoming a haunting spirit, Mayoi continues her quest to look for her mothers house, not knowing that she was turned into an oddity.</string>
    <string name="hanekawa_data">Tsubasa Hanekawa (Hanekawa Tsubasa) is Koyomi Araragi\'s classmate, close friend, and a class representative in Naoetsu Private High School. She is known at school as an overachiever and model student who is admired by many. However, hidden by her achievements in school and her kind personality is a tense family life caused by unfortunate circumstances.
She was bewitched by an oddity on the first day of Golden Week, giving birth to her "alternate self" called Black Hanekawa, and for some time was responsible for a series of attacks on various people in town.</string>
    <string name="kanbaru_data">Suruga Kanbaru (神原 駿河, Kanbaru Suruga) is Koyomi Araragi\'s underclassman, star player of the school\'s basketball team and one of Hitagi Senjougahara\'s acquaintances from junior high school. She is often seen having her left arm covered with bandages. Many people do not know that Kanbaru hides an oddity in the form of a "sentient" left arm.
It\'s revealed in Nisemonogatari by Deishuu Kaiki (and thought by Koyomi) that her mother\'s maiden name was Gaen. It\'s also revealed in Koimonogatari that her mother\'s name is Tooe Gaen. In Nekomonogatari White, it is also revealed that she used to be called Suruga Gaen.</string>
    <string name="karen_data">Karen Araragi (阿良々木 火憐, Araragi Karen) is the eldest of Koyomi Araragi\'s sisters and the older half of the Tsuganoki 2nd Middle School Fire Sisters (栂の木二中のファイヤーシスターズ, Tsuganoki Ni-chuu no Faiya Shisutazu).
She is a self-proclaimed "hero of justice" who often imitates the personality and quirks of various characters from tokusatsu series. Despite this, she is completely uninvolved with the supernatural, until she becomes victim to a certain oddity.</string>
    <string name="kissshot_data">Kiss-Shot Acerola-Orion Heart-Under-Blade. She generally is called this, depending on the person talking about her or her power level at the time. This vampire name was conceived by Deathtopia Virtuoso Suicide-Master, who was very proud of how meaningful the name is. Kiss-Shot, the first name, is a reference to the fairy tale of cursed princesses being healed by a kiss from a prince. This also mirrors Araragi, who saved her from death, and became her prince. Acerola-Orion, the middle name, is composed of Acerola, Princess Rolas self given alias after the start of her journey, and Orion, which is a constellation on the equator east of Taurus represented as a hunter with a belt and sword, which reflects her nature as a vampire, that being to hunt and eat humans, as well as furthers Deathtopias comparison of Princess Acerola to a sword. Finally, Heart-Under-Blade, the last name, is born from Deathtopias impressions of Princess Acerola as a strong woman, like a sword, but with a kind heart. This name is also the inspiration for the name Shinobu (忍), as it is literally made up of the kanji for heart (心) under the kanji for blade (刃).
It is understood that people who have known her, either directly or by reputation, call her by her full vampire name in all cases, exception made of the specialists close to Meme Oshino who was the one to adopt and name her Shinobu after she lost her power following Koyomi Vamp.
On the contrary, people close enough to Koyomi Araragi to be aware of her existence refer to her as Shinobu, as her child form is the only one they generally know of (exception made for Tsubasa Hanekawa).
Only Koyomi refers to her with both names, generally to referring to her according to her power level. Shinobu herself agrees that being weak changed her personality and that she knows her personality would probably revert to pre-Spring Break if she were to come back to being the powerful vampire she once was. Koyomi generally refers to her as Shinobu intimately, but doesn\'t hesitate to refer to her by her full vampire name when thinking about her, not wanting to forget her nature nor forgive her actions during Spring Break.
Intimately, only Koyomi and Seishirou Shishirui called her by the nickname Kiss-shot in front of her. However, most people referring to her vampire nature abridge her name this way behind her back.</string>
    <string name="nadeko_data">Nadeko Sengoku (千石 撫子, Sengoku Nadeko) is Tsukihi Araragis childhood friend and an acquaintance of Tsukihis brother Koyomi Araragi. She was a victim of a painful curse that caused an invisible snake to coil around her and manifest scars that resemble snake scales. During her attempts to cure herself of the curse, she met Koyomi once again after not seeing him for a long time.
She is the narrator of Otorimonogatari, Nademonogatari, and an arc in Yoimonogatari. She is the titular protagonist of three main arcs: Nadeko Snake, Nadeko Medusa, and Nadeko Draw, and three minor arcs: Nadeko Pool, Nadeko Mirror, and Kimi to Nadekko!</string>
    <string name="ononoki_data">Yotsugi Ononoki (Ononoki Yotsugi) is an expressionless human corpse tsukumogami and the shikigami familiar of Yozuru Kagenui. She\'s a somewhat unique take on both of the terms that define her, as tsukumogami are normally described as tools or objects that have come to life after years of neglect, and shikigami are typically depicted as being spirits or ghosts that are bound to an onmyouji master. In her case, she\'s a corpse that was neglected but brought back to life, and a shikigami in the sense that she\'s a "spirit" that is bound to her master.
Later in the series, she pretends to be Tsukihi Araragi\'s doll and lives in the Araragi household in order to protect Koyomi Araragi.
She is the narrator of an arc in Orokamonogatari and the titular protagonist of three main arcs: Yotsugi Doll, Yotsugi Body, and Yotsugi Shadow, and of two minor arcs: Yotsugi Future, and Yotsugi Stress.</string>
    <string name="senjougahara_data">Hitagi Senjougahara (戦場ヶ原 ひたぎ, Senjōgahara Hitagi) is a third-year student of Naoetsu Private High School. She is considered to be a frail-looking girl with an "incurable disease" and is distant from others.
In an accidental encounter with Koyomi Araragi, her closely kept secret is exposed, and triggers a life-changing experience. In the course of the series she receives the nickname Gahara and uses the alias Senshougahara.</string>
    <string name="shinobu_data">Shinobu Oshino (忍野 忍, Oshino Shinobu) is a mysterious vampire girl who acts as Meme Oshino\'s companion in the ruins of Eikou Cram School. Later in the series, she resides in Koyomi Araragi\'s shadow during the day.
She was formerly a human child princess named Rola (likely meant to be Laura in English) who was cursed into causing anyone in proximity to her to commit suicide. She then took the name of Acerola before meeting a purebred vampire that turned her into a powerful vampire named Kiss-Shot Acerola-Orion Heart-Under-Blade (キスショット・アセロラオリオン・ハートアンダーブレード, Kisushotto Aseroraorion Hātoandāburēdo). She now takes the form of an eight-year-old girl with another new name after losing most of her powers.</string>
    <string name="tsukihi_data">Tsukihi Araragi (阿良々木 月火, Araragi Tsukihi) is the supposed younger sister of both Koyomi Araragi and Karen Araragi, and the youngest member of the Araragi family. She is the younger half of the Tsuganoki Second Junior High School\'s Fire Sisters. She is unknowingly an offspring of the Shide no Tori, making her a fake human and giving her traits similar to that of a phoenix.
She is nicknamed Rara by her childhood friend Nadeko Sengoku. She is the titular protagonist of two main arcs: Tsukihi Phoenix and Tsukihi Undo, and of two minor arcs: Tsukihi Eternal and Tsukihi Brushing.</string>
</resources>
